

## **NGUYEN VAN A**

## **MARKETING MANAGER**

Male

**May 19, 1992** 

♥ Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and nnot foresee the pain and trouble that are bound of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

## **EDUCATION**



## **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. ional 'ing' or 'y' thrown in. It's ironic that administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

## **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. corporate administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

## **EXPERIENCE**



Sep 2007 - Present

### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

## Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult d a set of dry-transfer sheet and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

## **Recognition and Gains:**

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

## **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

## Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to scing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliq goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

## **ACTIVITIES**



Sep 2003 - 2007

## **CVPRO JSC**

### Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer it's seen all around the web; on tem' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

## **CERTIFICATIONS**



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2004

## HONORS & AWARDS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2013 - 2014

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US any variations of passages of Lor

## **REFERENCES**



## **NGUYEN VAN BINH**

director of cvpro jsc

## **SKILLS**



Words Photoshop

Excel English

Power Point Japanese

## **INTERESTS**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scrambled it to make a type specimen book. It has surv and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities